<BREAKFAST_menu>
<food>
<name>French Toast </name>
<description>
Fresh strawberries, blueberries & whipped cream,
dulce de leche sauce or Nutella sauce.
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>Fried Chicken and waffles </name>
<description>
A fresh made to order combination of breast, leg, and wing. 
Marinated in chef's own recipe, accompanied with a Belgium waffle
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>Corn Meal Cakes </name>
<description>
Cakes made with fresh corn, red peppers and white cheddar cheese. 
Served with smoked Virginia ham, two eggs any style and roasted red pepper sauce
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>Steak and Eggs </name>
<description>
Grilled Steak served with sauteed mushrooms, 
two eggs any style and house potatoes.
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>Croissant Sandwich </name>
<description>
Grilled croissant sandwich filled with two scrambled eggs,
 white cheddar cheese and Virginia ham. Served with house potatoes.
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>Omelets & Eggs </name>
<description>
Eggs dishes are served with Wheat, White, or Rye Toast. 
Choice of roasted breakfast potatoes, fresh fruit, or sliced tomatoes. 
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>Breakfast Burrito</name>
<description>
Scrambled eggs, onions, avocado, tomatoes, melted with pepper
jack cheese and sour cream. Wrapped in a flour tortilla, and guajillo sauce.
Choice of house potatoes or fresh fruit. 
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>FARMER'S CHOICE BREAKFAST</name>
<description>
This scratch-made feast is big enough to feed any hungry farmer. Our signature breakfast includes your choice of Bob Evans famous breakfast meat, alongside two fresh-cracked eggs cooked-to-order and hash browns, home fries or grits. Served with three griddled-to-perfection hotcakes or two slices of hand-dipped and griddled Brioche French toast. 
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>CLASSIC BREAKFAST</name>
<description>
Two eggs cooked-to-order, two hotcakes or one slice of Brioche French toast served with choice of premium breakfast meat.
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>COUNTRY FRIED STEAK & FARM FRESH EGGS</name>
<description>
Lightly breaded tender premium beef smothered with country gravy and served with two farm-fresh eggs cooked-to-order. Also includes your choice of hash browns, home fries or grits and freshly-baked bread.
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>FRUITFUL FARMER</name>
<description>
For a fresh start to your day. Hotcakes or Brioche French toast topped with fresh strawberries and bananas. Two fresh-cracked eggs cooked-to-order, served with your choice of breakfast meat and hash browns, home fries or grits.
</description>
</food>
</BREAKFAST_menu>


<!--  free gluten, dairy, another type egg  -->


<food>
<name>Duck Eggs</name>
<description>
For a fresh start to your day. Hotcakes or Brioche French toast topped with fresh strawberries and bananas. Two fresh-cracked eggs cooked-to-order, served with your choice of breakfast meat and hash browns, home fries or grits.
</description>
</food>


<food>
<name>Gluten-free Pancakes</name>
<description>
For a fresh start to your day. Hotcakes or Brioche French toast topped with fresh strawberries and bananas. Two fresh-cracked eggs cooked-to-order, served with your choice of breakfast meat and hash browns, home fries or grits.
</description>
</food>


<food>
<name>Gluten-free Waffles, French Toast with Bacon and Fruit</name>
<description>
For a fresh start to your day. Hotcakes or Brioche French toast topped with fresh strawberries and bananas. Two fresh-cracked eggs cooked-to-order, served with your choice of breakfast meat and hash browns, home fries or grits.
</description>
</food>