<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="dessert.xsl"?>
<DESSERT_menu>
<DESSERT>
<name>CINNAMON PULL APART </name>
<description>
Two pieces of soft, buttery bread coated in cinnamon sugar, baked gooey and topped with cream cheese icing.
</description>
</DESSERT>
<DESSERT>
<name>CARAMEL SUNDAE </name>
<description>
A scoop of creamy vanilla ice cream layered with caramel, finished with whipped topping.
</description>
</DESSERT>
<DESSERT>
<name>CHOCOLATE FUDGE SUNDAE </name>
<description>
A scoop of creamy vanilla ice cream layered with chocolate fudge, finished with whipped topping.
</description>
</DESSERT>
<DESSERT>
<name>DOUBLE CRUST APPLE PIE</name>
<description>
Our Double-Crust Apple Pie is filled with crisp, tart Michigan apples and cinnamon and then baked to crispy, flaky perfection.
</description>
</DESSERT>
<DESSERT>
<name>Classic Vanilla Cheesecake</name>
<description>
Creamy vanilla cheesecake on a graham cracker crust topped with your choice of strawberries in syrup or drizzled with chocolate or caramel sauce.
</description>
</DESSERT>
<DESSERT>
<name>Fudge Cake</name>
<description>
Decadent layers of moist cake with smooth fudge icing.
</description>
</DESSERT>
<DESSERT>
<name>Hot Fudge Brownie Sundae</name>
<description>
Is there anything more mouth-watering than those four words? Yup. Keep reading. Enjoy a decadent double chocolate brownie served warm with a scoop of creamy vanilla ice cream. Drizzled with butterscotch and chocolate sauce, topped with whipped cream and a Maraschino cherry.
</description>
</DESSERT>
<DESSERT>
<name>Lemon Meringue Pie</name>
<description>
Tall with a velvet-smooth texture. Sweet yet lemony. Have you worked it out yet? It's our much-loved Lemon Meringue Pie. It didn't become a classic by accident - you voted for it with your forks.
</description>
</DESSERT>
<DESSERT>
<name>Coconut Cream Pie</name>
<description>
Sometimes you just have to have pie. Not that mathematical type, but light, fluffy Coconut Cream Pie.
</description>
</DESSERT>
<DESSERT>
<name>Ice Cream</name>
<description>
Choose between chocolate or vanilla.
</description>
</DESSERT>
</DESSERT_menu>