<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="food.xsl"?>

<food_menu>
<food>
<name>HOMESTYLE BONE-IN FRIED CHICKEN</name>
<description>
This hand-breaded comfort classic is cooked to golden-crispy and juicy perfection. A plate filling portion will certainly leave you full and happy. 
 Served with your choice of sides and freshly baked bread.
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>HOMESTYLE FRIED CHICKEN TENDERS</name>
<description>
Oversized, premium cut all-white-meat chicken tenders. Cooked to golden-crusted perfection. Crispy on the outside, juicy on the inside, served with your choice of two sides and bread.
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>GRILLED TO PERFECTION CHICKEN</name>
<description>
Marinated boneless chicken breasts. Served with your choice of two farmhouse sides and freshly baked bread.
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>HERB-RUBBED TURKEY and DRESSING</name>
<description>
Ohioans know the key to any good turkey is time. That's why our real turkey breast is slow-roasted in our kitchens for hours with our new savory blend of herbs and spices. Served with homestyle gravy, your choice of sides, cranberry relish and freshly-baked bread.
</description>
</food>

<food>
<name>HANDCRAFTED DELI TURKEY SANDWICH</name>
<description>
Shaved Signature slow-roasted turkey, Swiss cheese, lettuce, tomatoes, onion and roasted tomato mayo on marble wheat bread. Served with your choice of sides.
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name> Turkey Burger</name>
<description>
 An all-white meat, flame-broiled turkey burger with Vermont Cheddar cheese, lettuce, fresh pico de gallo and guacamole
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name> Cheese Burger</name>
<description>
A classic, can’t-go-wrong favorite. Comes with American,
Vermont Cheddar or Swiss cheese
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>CHICKEN and NOODLES</name>
<description>
Thick country-style egg noodles, slow-roasted, all-white-meat chicken and vegetables simmered in a rich broth
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>CHEDDAR BAKED POTATO SOUP</name>
<description>
Homestyle cuts of russet potatoes in a seasoned cheese sauce garnished with bacon and scallions.
</description>
</food>
<food>
<name>HEARTY BEEF VEGETABLE SOUP</name>
<description>
Tender beef slow-cooked in a tomato broth loaded with farm vegetables: carrots, corn, tomatoes, potatoes, celery and onions.
</description>
</food>
</food_menu>